LEO - LAM NGUYEN

CONTACT

Address: Toronto ON
Phone: 647 864 4338

Email: leonguyen.to@gmail.com

LINKS

• Portfolio: www.itsmeleo.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in /leolamnguyen/

SKILLS

- Digital content generation
- Organization, prioritizing, and multitasking
- · Adobe Creative Suite
- MS Office
- Problem resolution
- Relationship development
- Social Media Technologies
- · Web Design
- UX Design
- HTML
- CSS
- · Web development projects

VOLUNTEER WORK

- 2015: The 7th European Vietnamese Documentary Film Festival
- 2017: Toronto International Film Festival (TIFF)
- 2018: Toronto International Film Festival (TIFF)

EDUCATION

Post-Degree Certificate: Website Development, 09/2022 **Humber College** - Toronto, ON

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Performance-driven advertising/web design student motivated to solve all web-based needs. Have experience in creating designs, sample layouts and concepts and generating new ideas with limited direction. With superior work ethic and good teamwork, problem-solving and organizational skills. Proficient in developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript.

WORK HISTORY

Wine Merchant, 09/2021 to Current Wine Rack - Toronto, ON

- Built customer loyalty and retention by delivering excellent shopping experiences.
- Created inviting environment for customers by maintaining store organization and cleanliness.
- Listened to customer needs and desires to identify and recommend optimal products.
- Prioritized helping customers over completing other routine tasks in store.
- · Managed efficient cash register operations.
- Answered customer questions about products and services, helped locate merchandise and promoted key items.

Social Media Intern, 01/2021 to 07/2021 **Admission Hub** - Toronto, ON

- Responded to comments, posts and questions from various channels under the supervision of the Social Media Manager.
- Assisted Social Media Coordinators with various marketing projects that would engage new leads and potential customers.
- Created engaging content to catch the attention of potential customers.
- Conducted daily updates to social media profiles to boost company online presence.
- Analyzed trends in social media posts and followers to maximize views.
- Created content strategies for digital media.

Marketing Intern, 06/2020 to 08/2020 CheaprEats - Toronto, ON

- Modernized web pages and updated social media presence as part of comprehensive strategies to enhance customer engagement.
- Tracked and analyzed web analytics to recommend proactive adjustments to strategies.
- Worked with other team members to synchronize web presence with brand identity and logo.
- Designed graphics for websites, logos and promotions for marketing

Bachelor of Creative Advertising: Advertising, 08/2021 **Humber College** - Toronto, ON

Bachelor of Applied Art: Media Production And Management, 06/2016 **Lotus University** - Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam purposes.

- Collaborated with team members to help expand marketing channels.
- Performed market analysis and researched latest trends.

Marketing Intern, 06/2019 to 08/2019 Campbell Immigration Law Firm - Toronto, ON

- Contributed to mock-ups, email campaigns and social media content.
- Designed and presented social media campaign ideas.
- Stayed updated with the latest marketing concepts and techniques.
- Helped clients develop website portals and social media pages to promote businesses.
- Designed graphics for websites, logos and promotions for marketing purposes.
- Provided administrative support to senior staff including creating proposals and organizing documentation.